what obscure piece we will be starting
soon presentation starts at 2:00 p.m.
Nebraska time I don't know what time
that is California time but it's soon I
think the minute said the same two hours
different yeah that's yes the same
minutes
so whenever the minutes go to zero zero
that's when the presentation will start
maybe we'll give everyone a few minutes
we got a bit of a crowd here
this is offseason for the college so
yeah nutshell four products what we got
a minute here's like here's a 128
gigabyte beyond that will be available
for sale right here in Omaha we have a
box full of comma a I Pandits we are
gonna be presenting some vanilla gorilla
and we have a Toyota giraffe right here
midnight black who's talking about
midnight black where'd you hear about
midnight black all right we got
something we got some people here we got
some media here we're gonna be nice to
the media on the tour yeah some of the
some of the cities are fake news am I
gonna talk about slam no I'm going to
talk about slam it's a pretty
straightforward overview presentation
it's gonna be similar to my web summit
presentation but with less
Bitcoin casual wallet no and I got to
talk about Bitcoin cash though if you
guys want to check out something new I
found it last night it's called the
Swift life it's the number two app in
the App Store it is a social network
which gives you direct access to Taylor
Swift and you guys know that I'm a
telescope fan so you guys might want to
download the Swift life I'm a level two
on the Swift life I'm working on might a
Moche game you got to get tame oh geez
just show these people don't even pay me
man
no no there won't really be unveilings
slam anything on mapping I know nothing
new I mean you got to realize that a lot
of people who are coming here don't
really know that much about us so it's a
pretty you have made , for trains with
overspeed warning seriously oh no it's
it's really sad whenever trans crash I'm
just like dude positive train control
has existed for years unions are killing
people yeah I'm excited for the future
too I love I love the future you guys
know I love the future
how many disengage events a lot it's
like what is so you know we're a little
beyond 1 every 10 miles now so we've
driven like 2,000 miles probably around
two other we can we can maybe compiled
together some statistics on number of
just engagements any insurance stuff you
guys know I'm not talking about
businessmen am I missing for hacking no
not really
self-driving cars I like winning you
know all right
and wait two more minutes guys two more
minutes
I know it's as bad as The Bachelor when
they're like who's gonna get the rose
The Bachelor was the original
Bachelorette see the video of the pilot
port or you guys got one off that's
pretty sweet so how did this go please
go
I thought you didn't let go your voice
I'm so tired I don't watch your voice
your voice sounds great on periscope no
I just wanna say how do you guys um
shame about slam if you want to talk
about slam sometime we'll talk about
slam some time you know me
no secrets bro no secrets bros five
minutes come in and come into the come
into the scope II lounge throwing all
these people
I'm good I'm good
okay I got my I got my collar beanie on
am I about to give a talk yes how's the
weather it's a little cold um am I still
working on deep learning slam sort of
yeah kind of we're working on supervised
depth Nets I'm like slammer core is
memory and deep learning doesn't really
work well with memory so there's that
like people talk about it but it's it's
no memory right whereas like slam in a
room is quite different from slam on a
road any tips for people working on
self-driving cars join us or die that
that is gonna be one of the themes of
2018 and the other theme is gonna be
outwit outplay outlast I came up with
that myself don't think I ripped that
off now you all know I ripped it off you
all know you don't know am i nervous I
swear to god I ain't nervous you know
the Lil Wayne Lil Wayne
all the way men that guy's a genius no
I'm really not nervous hats for sale we
don't sell the hats and guys if you
think hoodies are overpriced now we're
gonna we're gonna be like Martin shkreli
where we're raising those prices all
right we're ready to start cool who's
who's holding was holding Muskogee's
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
what makes a car after